discountcell.com 2013-08-17

# Privacy Statement for Discountcell.com

## About Us

This is a privacy policy for Discountcell.com. Our homepage on the Web is located at [ http://www.discountcell.com](http://www.discountcell.com/). 

We invite you to contact us if you have questions about this policy. You may contact us by mail at the following address: 

    Discountcell.com
    350 West 500 South
    Provo, Utah 84601 
    United States of America

You may contact us by e-mail at [ Info@discountcell.com](mailto:Info@discountcell.com). You may call us at 1-800-422-1814. 

**What information do we collect?**

We collect information from you when you place an order, subscribe to our newsletter or fill out a form. 

When ordering or registering on our site, as appropriate, you may be asked to enter your: name, e-mail address, mailing address, phone number or credit card information. You may, however, visit our site anonymously.

Like most websites, we use cookies and/or web beacons to enhance your experience, gather general visitor information, and track visits to our website. Please refer to the 'do we use cookies?' section below for information about cookies and how we use them.

 **What do we use your information for?**

Any of the information we collect from you may be used in one of the following ways: 

• To personalize your experience  
(your information helps us to better respond to your individual needs)

• To improve our website  
(we continually strive to improve our website offerings based on the information and feedback we receive from you)

• To improve customer service  
(your information helps us to more effectively respond to your customer service requests and support needs)

• To process transactions  
Your information, whether public or private, will not be sold, exchanged, transferred, or given to any other company for any reason whatsoever, without your consent, other than for the express purpose of delivering the purchased product or service requested by the customer. 

• To send periodic emails

The email address you provide for order processing will only be used to send you information and updates pertaining to your order.

If you choose to subscribe to our newsletter you may be sent occasional company news, updates, related product or service information, etc.

Note: If at any time you would like to unsubscribe from receiving future emails, we include detailed unsubscribe instructions at the bottom of each email.

 **How do we protect your information?**

We implement a variety of security measures to maintain the safety of your personal information when you place an order or access your personal information. 

We offer the use of a secure server. All supplied sensitive/credit information is transmitted via Secure Socket Layer (SSL) technology and then encrypted into our Database to be only accessed by those authorized with special access rights to our systems, and are required to keep the information confidential. 

After a transaction, your private information (credit card information) will not be kept on file for more than 30 days.

 **Do we use cookies?**

Yes (Cookies are small files that a site or its service provider transfers to your computers hard drive through your Web browser (if you allow) that enables the sites or service providers systems to recognize your browser and capture and remember certain information

We use cookies to help us remember and process the items in your shopping cart, understand and save your preferences for future visits and compile aggregate data about site traffic and site interaction so that we can offer better site experiences and tools in the future. We may contract with third-party service providers to assist us in better understanding our site visitors. These service providers are not permitted to use the information collected on our behalf except to help us conduct and improve our business.

If you prefer, you can choose to have your computer warn you each time a cookie is being sent, or you can choose to turn off all cookies via your browser settings. Like most websites, if you turn your cookies off, some of our services may not function properly. However, you can still place orders over the telephone.

 **Do we disclose any information to outside parties?**

We do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your personally identifiable information. This does not include trusted third parties who assist us in operating our website, conducting our business, or servicing you, so long as those parties agree to keep this information confidential. We may also release your information when we believe release is appropriate to comply with the law, enforce our site policies, or protect ours or others rights, property, or safety. 

**Third party links**

Occasionally, at our discretion, we may include or offer third party products or services on our website. These third party sites have separate and independent privacy policies. We therefore have no responsibility or liability for the content and activities of these linked sites. Nonetheless, we seek to protect the integrity of our site and welcome any feedback about these sites.

 **California Online Privacy Protection Act Compliance**

Because we value your privacy we have taken the necessary precautions to be in compliance with the California Online Privacy Protection Act. We therefore will not distribute your personal information to outside parties without your consent.

 **Childrens Online Privacy Protection Act Compliance**

We are in compliance with the requirements of COPPA (Childrens Online Privacy Protection Act), we do not collect any information from anyone under 13 years of age. Our website, products and services are all directed to people who are at least 13 years old or older.

 **Terms and Conditions**

Please also visit our Terms and Conditions section establishing the use, disclaimers, and limitations of liability governing the use of our website at http://www.discountcell.com/legal.htm.

 **Your Consent**

By using our site, you consent to our privacy policy.

 **Changes to our Privacy Policy**

If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on this page. 

**Contacting Us**

If there are any questions regarding this privacy policy you may contact us using the information below. 

www.discountcell.com  
350 West 500 South  
Provo, UT 84601  
United States  
info@discountcell.com  
801-235-9809

* * *

## Compact Policy Summary

The compact policy which corresponds to this policy is: 

        CP="IDC CURa ADMa AIa OUR DELa BUS UNI PUR COM NAV STA"

The following table explains the meaning of each field in the compact policy. 

**Field**|  **Meaning**  
---|---  
`CP=` | This is the compact policy header; it indicates that what follows is a P3P compact policy.  
`IDC` |  Access is available to contact information.   
`CURa` |  The data is used for completion of the current activity.   
`ADMa` |  The data is used for site administration.   
`DEVa` |  The data is used for research and development.   
`TAIa` |  The data is used for tailoring the site.   
`CONa` |  The data is used for contacting the user.   
`OUR` |  The data is given to ourselves and our agents.   
`DELa` |  The data is given to delivery services.   
`BUS` |  Our business practices specify how long the data will be kept.   
`IND` |  The data will be kept indefinitely.   
`PHY` |  Physical contact information is collected.   
`ONL` |  Online contact information is collected.   
`UNI` |  Unique identifiers are collected.   
`PUR` |  Purchase information is collected.   
`COM` |  Computer information is collected.   
`NAV` |  Navigation and clickstream data is collected.   
`DEM` |  Demographic and socioeconomic data is collected.   
`STA` |  State-management data is collected   
  
The compact policy is sent by the Web server along with the cookies it describes. For more information, see the P3P deployment guide at <http://www.w3.org/TR/p3pdeployment>. 

* * *

* * *

---|---|---|---|---|---|---|---  
  
We keep your device running with only authentic, top quality **[cell phone accessories](http://www.discountcell.com/ "cell phone accessories")**.  Buy with confidence knowing every item we offer is covered by our satisfaction guarantee and the manufacturers warranty.

*$.99 cent shipping (free over $50) only applies to orders shipping within the Continental US.

[Discountcell](http://www.discountcell.com/) is a certified woman owned company through the WBENC.

For questions or comments please contact Info@DiscountCell.com.  
Copyright 1997-2013 Discountcell all Rights Reserved.   Discountcell is a trademark of Discountcell Inc.  
350 West 500 South, Provo UT 84601
